Yesterday I talked to an old man from the
Я вчера общался с дедушкой из
Belgorod region and this old man
Белгородской области и эта дедушка
says that he is
говорит что его
being resettled because of the war and people from Belgorod have
отселить войну а люди из Белгорода
now been
теперь
evacuated. And I'll tell you, this is a
эвакуированы А я вам скажу это
Ukrainian adventure, it's super, I like this kind of
украинская авантюра это супер мне такая
adventure. I would like to have such an
авантюра нравится Я бы хотел такую
adventure in the Bryansk
авантюру ещё в Брянской
region. Good evening.
области Добрый вечер
Hello, about the World Cup, a conversation with Veta and
Здравствуйте о ЧМ беседу Вете
Russians about the
с россиянами о
war. And where are you from? I'm from
войне А вы откуда будете Я сам из
Khmelnitsky. Where are you from? Belgorod region, Belgorod
Хмельницкого Вы
region, more specifically. I told you, Belgorod region, well, more specifically, Belgorod region, Belgorod. Well, specifically Belgorod itself
белгородчина Белгород Ну конкретно сам
or somewhere in the region. If from the
Белгород или где-то из области если из
region, then what kind of Belgorod. I understood everything. Belgorod, do
области то какой на Белгород всё понял
n't burn Belgorod. Belgorod.
Белгород та Горите не Белгород Белгород
I would understand how you are doing with the
я бы понял как там у вас с
shelling. In what sense have you
обстрелами В каком смысле хорошо вас
been found well or
обрели или
badly, much less than before, this is
плохо намного меньше чем было раньше это
bad, this is our oversight. I did
плохо это наша недоработка Я вчера с
a deal with one old man yesterday. And how are you being
одним дедушкой сдел А вас как
shelled? And we are not being shelled. In
обстреливают А нас не обстреливают в
Mininsky, everything is fine. Yesterday I
мининском вообще всё хорошо Я вчера
talked to an old man from the Belgorod
общался с дедушкой из Белгородской
region and this old man says.  that he should be
области и эта дедушка говорит что его
resettled because he is now in a
отселить потому что он сейчас в пункте
temporary accommodation point How is it
временного размещения Как так получается
that they started a war and people from Belgorod have
что начали войну а люди из Белгорода
now been
теперь
evacuated And I will tell you this is a
эвакуированы А я вам скажу это
Ukrainian adventure this is super I
украинская авантюра это супер мне такая
like such an adventure I would like such an
авантюра нравится Я бы хотел такую
adventure in the Bryansk region it is good Do
авантюру ещ в Брянской области хорошо Вы
n't worry if you like it it's not a big
не переживайте если вам нравится это
deal you like it even more
ничего страшного нравится вам ещё больше
When will they enter the Kharkov Sumy
Когда будет войдут в харьковскую сумскую
region Oh my God so you have already left
область Ой Боже Боже так вы же уже вышли
Kharkov from the Sumy region no and we
из Харьковской из Сумской области нет и
will You you entered in the very first
будем Вы же вы же зашли в самые первые
days you entered the Kharkov Sumy
дни вы зашли в харьковскую сумскую
region And now you left like that and we are
область А теперь вы вышли так и мы и
there now so you left from there More precisely you did not
сейчас там так вы вышли оттуда Точнее не
leave but ran out I repeat once again We are where
вышли а выбежали раз повторяю Мы ещё раз
you are again there and you are not in the
там где вы ещё раз там и вас нету в
Sumy region in the Khavskaya you ran away
Сумской области в хавской вы убежали
from there then you were kicked out such a ua gave
оттуда тогда вас выгнали такой уа дали
you you ran away ha Listen here I
вам вы убежали ха Слушай сюды я тебе
tell you to name the area Where are we
район говорю назвать Где мы находимся
Where
Где ты
are you Pisarevka Pisarevka Kumskaya
находишься писаревка писаревка кумская
region how much  there Pisarevka we
область сколько там писаревки мы
are in the Kursk region Look they
находимся в Курской области Смотри мне
brought me yes uh removed from the car in the Kursk
привезли да ээ сняли с машины в Курской
region Look further Let's go there for Suzha
области Смотри дальше Давай туда за сужа
Suzha this is how they lured you to Pisarevka You were
сужа это вас в Писарев заманили вас
lured to Pisarevka And in Sudzha
заманили в писаревка А в Судже как раз
everything is fine there even foreign
всё хорошо там даже иностранные
journalists are driving around filming look
журналисты катаются снимают смотрите
Russian And you
русские А вас
Kurt now everything is look Trump came Yes it was
Курт сейчас всё смотри Трамп пришёл Да
this Biden who didn't give weapons and
это этот байден типа не давал оружие а
Trump will finally give now he will say According to
Трамп наконец-то сейчас даст скажет По
this Kremlin and
этому Кремлю и
we to the Kremlin yes Congratulations to you Trump Trump is
мы Кремлю да Поздравляю вас трампом
cool Trump of all I was for Trump
Трамп классный Трамп коне Я за трампа
yes Because when Trump was there they gave
был да Потому что когда был Трамп давали
Russia they gave Iran Siri now
России давали ирану Сири сейчас
finally because this old man this
наконец-то потому что этот дед этот
Biden Yes he is in short some kind of and Trump he is
байден Да он короче какой-то а Трамп он
really a rock he will now call Putin
реально скал он сейчас Путину позвонит
yes on oppression you in short and say go
да на гнёт вас короче и скажет идите вы
all of you that's why Zelensky is not God
все вот так поэтому Зеленского не Боже
look America it is profitable for America to destroy the
смотри Америке Америке выгодно развалить
Russian Federation Yes why does America need uh
Российскую Федерацию Да зачем Америке ээ
if America will give more
если Америка да будет давать больше
weapons to Ukraine for  that we
оружия Украине для того чтобы мы
shell the Russian Federation This is
обстреливали Российскую Федерацию Это
America's plus America needs this America does
плюс Америки Америке это нужно Америка
n't want to shell it itself and
же не хочет сама обстреливать это и
guys well what are you panting
ребята ну то что ты там панты колоти сь
about it So now tell me tell me why you ca
на это Так теперь скажи скажи почему вы
n't already 3 months today is the sixth
не можете уже 3 месяца сегодня шестое 6
November 6th exactly 3 months August 6th the
ноября ровно 3 месяца 6 августа началось
Ukrainian liberation of the Kursk region began
украинское освобождение Курской области
and look this is a trophy number from the
да и смотри это трофейный номер из
Kursk region Yes some kind of this
Курской области Да какой-то этот
Mitsubishi If ninety-eighth year is
Mitsubishi Коль девяносто восьмого года
rolling around somewhere now without this number
где-то катается теперь без этого номера
How is it that you can't
Как так получается что вы не можете
defend a nuclear power can't
защищать ядерное держава не может
defend its forty-sixth region forty-
защитить свой сорок шестой регион сорок
sixth Why why can't you and because
шестой Почему почему не можете а потому
your green will be screwed So wait I'll screw you and
что вашего зеле кинут Так подожди кину а
now you have been unable to liberate for 3 months
сейчас вы 3 месяца уже не можете
and what will Trump say Trump will
освободить и что Трамп скажет Трамп
say Look this is cool Kursk region is
скажет Смотри это круто Курская область
under the control of Ukraine So why then uh do we
под контролем Украины Так зачем тогда ээ
need to strain yes we need to strain Putin and
надо напрягать да надо напрячь Путина и
say Putin you are giving away Kursk Bryansk
сказать Путин отдаёшь курскую брянскую
region
область
Belgorod Voronezh Rostov So
Белгородскую воронежскую ростовскую Так
this will be a buffer zone yes under a mandate  there will
это будет буферная зона да под мандатом
be Ukrainian peacekeepers there to keep
он там будут украинские Миротворцы
everything calm
стоять чтобы короче было всё спокойно
so that there is no looting by the Russian army
чтобы не было мародёрство русской армии
and so on Russia will
и так дальше Россия будет
disarm the turf will not have
разоружения дерно оружия не будет иметь
heavy weapons and will disintegrate
тяжёлой тяжёлого вооружения и распадётся
into 33 small states and each
на 33 маленьких государства и в каждом
state will have its own flag and its own number yes yes
государстве свой флаг и свой номер да
Instead of this little flag Vlasov
Дада Вот вместо этого флажка Власов
will have other flags yes Well let's
будут другие флаги да А ну давай
listen to you But when the
послушаем тебя А вот когда зайдут
Russians go there you will be the first to start Where Where will the
россияне туда ты ж первый нач Куда Куда
Russians go They have already gone near
зайдут россияне Они же уже заходили под
Kyiv nothing And why why explain to me
Киев ничего А почему почему объясни мне
Listen Let's talk normally Let's
Слушай Давай нормально поговорим Давай
try to talk normally And why did the
попробуем нормально поговорить А почему
Russians run away from
россияне убежали изд
Kyiv do you want to show yourself smart Well
Киева из хочешь показать себя умного Ну
explain why the Russians ran away from
объясни почему россияне убежали из-под
Kiev They were in Kyiv in the Kharkov
Киева Они же были в Киеве в Харьковской
region in Kherson Yes why did they
области в Херсоне Да почему они
run away Why did they run away Why aren't you
убежали Почему убежали Почему ты не
defending your Kursk region Explain
защищаешь свою курскую область Объясни
why you attacked your Russia
почему ты на твою Россию напали Да
Now look they are taking away license plates from cars Yes
сейчас смотри забирают номера с машин Да
pregnant grandfathers And here you are sitting and not
беременных дедушек Да вот и ты сидишь не
defending  sit in the toilet You by the way in the
защищаешь сиди в туалете Ты ты кстати в
toilet on the
туалете на
toilet
унитазе
[music]
[музыка]
Russian wait stop you are sitting in the toilet
российски подожди стоп ты в туалете
and you every day one Two la one
сидишь и Вы каждый день одно Два ла одно
Minute Minute wait you are sitting in the
Минуту Минуту подожди ты в туалете
toilet you are sitting in the toilet yes that is you are
сидишь ты в туалете сидишь да то есть ты
sitting now while you are sitting
сейчас сидишь пока ты сидишь
on sha taesh Belash you can't until you Take a
на ша таешь Белаш не можешь пока не
[ __ ] with a Ukrainian Let's help you
Посри с украинцем Давай мы тебе Поможем
Let's Tusya shsya Yes Kursk region is no longer there you don't have you Kursk region
Давай Туся шся Да Курской область уже
Let's Kursk region
нету у вас нету вы курскую область Давай
And you can't I'll tell
курскую область А ты не можешь расскажу
you Look Kursk region You
тебе Смотри курскую область Ты
look look Yes you Kursk region And you ca
смотри смотри Да вы курскую область А ты
n't your stomach
не можешь свой желудок
Yes why why look
Да почему почему смотри
at soshe region it's hard to
на соше регион призна тяжело коне
admit it's hard for you to admit that you are sitting on the
признать тяжело тебе что ты сидишь на
toilet and can't can't until you
унитазе и не можешь не можешь пока не
tell the Ukrainians something evil Yes you have
скажешь украинцам что-то злое Да у тебя
already blocked everything up yes That's right Because
закупорила уже всё да Правильно Потому
from your fury from anger everything is already
что от люти твоей от гнева там всё уже
shaved there ambassador Well you are you are really You are on  you're
обрит послу Ну ты ты же реально Ты же на
sitting on the toilet
унитазе сидишь
yes, at least I'm on the toilet And you're sitting at the World Cup Well, you're on the
да я-то хоть на унитазе А ты на ЧМ сиди
toilet, damn, dude, you went out onto the
Ну ты на унитазе блин чувак ты вышел на
toilet Lelya in the Kursk region and let's
унитаз Лели в курскую область и давай
grab
хапать
bicycles Yes, we took them, we took them, we're
велосипеды Да мы забрали мы забрали мы
pragmatic, we took them from the Kursk
прагматичные мы забрали э с Курской
region, bicycles, washing machines,
области велосипеды стиральные машины
toilets Yes, and we'll come to Belgorod, we'll take
унитазы Да и придём в Белгород заберём
your toilet and you won't be able to sit on it You see, you won't be
твой унитаз и ты тебе не будет на сидеть
able to Show me the number,
Понимаешь ты не сможешь Покажи номер ты
look at the number for now, with the sixth And
на смотри номер пока с со шестой А тебе
for your happiness, to hold it in your hands Yes, for
за счастье в руках подержать Да за
happiness, I still have a
счастье у меня ещё вот тут стот ещё
big sign right here for Belgorod, well, it's going to be
стоит большой знак на Белгород ну его
broken now, in short, drag it out and unpack it Come on
сейчас слом короче тащить распаковать
And
Давай И
you'll be the first one, yes, you
ты первый же будешь
'll be burnt, burnt You're already on the
да будеш подгорел подгорел Ты уже как на
toilet a little bit, is it going or not, it's not working
унитазе немножко идёт идёт оно или нет
out,
не получается
Ukrainian, it's not working out for you Yes,
украинец не получается тебе Да вот
look, you sat down, you sat down on the toilet, you sat on the toilet, you're sitting on the toilet
смотри ты сел ты сел на ты сел на унитаз
in the corner Yes, that's what's
сидишь на унитазе в углу Да Угол это
called a corner, that's it,
называется вот да
and you're sitting and in short  you're sitting in a chat roulette
и ты сидишь и короче сидишь в чатрулетке
it's just
это просто
uh incredible incredible some kind of
э невероятный невероятный какой-то
andropharm
андрофарм
that you put your finger in your mouth And yes I'm
что пальчик ротику подносишь А да я
embarrassed to give you And why why do you have a
стесняюсь тебе дать А почему почему у
hole here
тебя дырочка тут а почему дырка кто
and why is there a hole
пробил и как дырку не что ты так просишь
who punched it and how is it a hole not what are you asking like that who punched a hole in you and how is it a hole I'm in your
кто пробил дырку тебе и
mouth No well who Look I don't have a hole in my mouth but you do why
Вот у меня нету дырки во рту а у тебя
explain I'll punch it Well
есть почему так объясни пробью Ну
explain just I don't understand why you
объясни просто я не понимаю почему
can't go and do it at the dentist
нельзя пойти и сделать у стоматолога
so that it's not there Well that's why you don't
чтобы её не было Ну ты ж поэтому ты не
understand well oh baby baby no And
понимаешь ну ой малышка малышка не А
lips And by the way how did you pump up your lips so much
губки А кстати как ты губы так накачал
really pumped up lips
реально подкачанный губи
like these made for the front line don't go
такие какие сделанные на передовую не ид
What because I'm waiting for you I'm
Какие потому что я тебя жду я же тебя
asking you why don't you go for protection I
спрашиваю почему ты не идёшь за щить я с
brought it from I brought this number from your Kursk region
я привёз я с твоей Курской области
Yes and why are you sitting
привёз этот номер Да а почему ты сидишь
on the toilet and can't protect Why ca
на унитазе и не можешь защитить Почему
n't you protect your Russia yes you
ты не можешь защитить свою Россию да
see look
видишь смотри
And the
А
phantoms called me
фантомасы меня называла
phantom, it's not enough Why are you sitting on the
фантомасе го мало Почему ты сидишь на
toilet and not in the trench Why are you on the
унитазе а не в окопе почему ты на
toilet and not in the trench Why why are you on the
унитазе а не в окопе Почему почему ты в
toilet and not in the trench explain Come on, come on, I
на унитазе а не в окопе объясни Давай
came from the front lines, but
давай я я с передовой пришёл а вот
show me, show me where you came You're
покажи покажи где ты пришёл Ты на
sitting on the toilet where you were on the
унитазе сидишь где ты был на
front lines, come on, show me what you I'll
передовой давай покажи что ты Я сейчас
show you now, here he stood up, stood up, come on, show me
покажу вот он встал
Oh,
встал давай покажи Ах
you,
ты
while here I am showing you, come on, what is this, you
пока вот я тебе показываю
sat down, in short, this is not a
ся давай что это ты сел короче это не
military uniform, this is not a military uniform you have Come on, you're not a military man, you're not a
военная форма это не военная форма у
military man,
тебя Давай ты не военный ты не военный
you're sitting on It's just that
ты сидишь на Просто
you just What did I do to you Look, I
ты просто А что я тебя Смотри я тебя
drove you off your toilet and you're
согнал с твоего унита и тыт
shocked by this, you know, there it is, in short, it will stick
шок от этого знаешь там оно короче заит
and there will be stones Come on, have a smoke, don't be nervous, don't be
и будут камни Да давай закури за
nervous Come on, have a smoke, have a smoke, got
нервничай закури за нервничай Давай
nervous
давай Покури Покури занервничал
[music]
[музыка]
honor, look, the flag is upside down
честь смотри флаг перевёрнутый
Russian varnish inverted Russian
российский лак перевёрнутый российский
you why why howled Why did you run away
ты почему почему выли Почему вы убежали
from Kursk region Why did you run away from
с Курской области Почему убежали с
Kursk region Listen By the way, why didn't you wash your
Курской области Слушай Кстати а почему
hands and wipe them with toilet
ты руки не помыл и не вытер туалетной
paper I'm yours Why didn't you wipe yours and
бумагой Я твою Почему ты не вытер свою и
wash your
не помыл
hands Why say Well, look, don't be nervous,
руки Почему скажи Ну смотри не нервничай
baby, they didn't
малыш не
let you on the toilet and go to chat roulette
дали на унитазе и выходить в чат рулетку
like pipska
лайк пиписка
comment hello hello let's have a
комент здравствуйте здравствуйте давайте
normal conversation
нормально пообщаемся
Of course, where are you
Конечно вы
from I'm from Kazan, not me, I meant from
откуда Я из Казани не я имел в виду из
which room This is a bathroom Yes, I
какой комнаты Это ванная комната Да я
understand that I mean from which
понимаю что я имею в виду из какой
room from the toilet Well,
комнаты из туалета
I'm just smoking I'm howling now
Да ну это я просто курю Это я сейчас выю
and I'll walk out of here Well, are you sitting on the toilet now
и выду отсюда Ну вы на унитазе сейчас
No And on what am I just smoking Well,
сидите Да нет А на чём я просто курю Ну
where are you sitting Well, not that one I agree
а где вы сидите Ну ну не та та согласен
yes but I smoke nothing like that Just show me
да но я курю ничего таких Просто покажи
I don't like Show that you're really
я не люблю Покажи что действительно вы
just sitting on the toilet and not so that I can have a
просто сидите на унитазе а не чтобы я
normal conversation I can't communicate
нормально пообщался я не могу общаться
if
если
people are video that you're just sitting for a second a
люди видео что вы просто сидите секунду
second you can yes  are you a normal person I
секунду можно да вы нормальный человек я
want to talk to you Yes, just so that
хочу с вами поговорить Да просто чтоб ну
I dont worry that youre somewhere lets
я не переживал что вы где-то давайте я
talk to you too Im even really
тоже хочу поговорить мне прямо даже
interested oh really interested
интересно
interesting op op op op op op
интересно оп оп оп оп оп оп
op everything like that is
оп всё вот такие вот
normal so we
нормальны так что мы
also just wanted to talk Are you from
ещё хотели просто пообщаться Вы из
Kazan Yes, Im originally from Rostov But Ive been living
Казани Да я сам родом из Ростова Но живу
in America in California for 18 years now in
в Америке в Калифорнии уже 18 лет через
2 years it will be 20 you
2 года будет двадцатом
work were waving its not
работаете машим
important
как бы неважно
right I dont think maybe you Maybe youre an
правильно не думаю может вы Может вы
athlete do you play hockey there or not
спортсмен там в хоккей играете или нет
no they say hockey is popular in Kazan
нет там в Казани популярный хоккей
Well yes, I understand listen how do you
говорят Ну да понял слушайте как вот вы
think that Russias attack on Ukraine has had a
считаете то что Россия напала на Украину
positive or negative impact on the economy of the
это позитивно отразилось на экономике
Russian Federation
Российской Федерации или
I think
негативно Я считаю
that a
что
plus so And how has it improved for you in the
а плюс так А чем Чем вам лучше стало в
economy just a plus So what
экономике просто плюс Так а в чём плюс
exactly is the plus the dollar is a plus Lets go Yes, I
конкретно доллар в плюс Пошёл Да
agree the dollar is a very
согласен доллар очень
plus No no no no No well the dollar used to be
плюс Нет нет нет не Нет ну доллар раньше
one now the dollar is a very big
был один теперь доллар очень большой
plus they
плюс
say somewhere plus 100% the dollar and prices are a
говорят где-то плюс 100% доллар и цены
say No well look Look look
говорят Нет ну смотрите Смотрите
and from America Im not saying that its a plus
а с Америки Я не говорю что плюс вот
honestly no Here with
честно По чесноку нет Вот с
[music]
[музыка]
mine Well no no no way Well yes in America it's
моей Ну нет ну нет никак Ну да в Америке
better here There's no market And how is it better in
лучше тут Базара нет А чем лучше в
Russia
России стало
Well they just started their own and that's all and that's it
Ну просто свою начали да и всё и вс не
Well look Here how much were your prices
Ну смотри Вот раньше сколько у вас цены
before and how much are they
были раньше и сколько
now what what else how much were your prices
сейчас что что ещ сколько у вас цены
before how much were they and how much are they now
раньше сколько были и сколько сейчас
prices are much higher much higher so prices are in the plus good Well how is it better no
цены в плюс хорошо Ну а чем лучше стало
And a lot of salaries are higher so salaries are
нет И много зарплаты выше так зарплаты
higher because
выше из-за того что
inflation prices are higher than salaries are growing
инфляция цены больше чем зарплата растёт
how much is your salary
сколько у вас зарплата
Now
Сейчас
a hundred is 1,000 dollars What do you
стольник 1.000 долларов вы кем
work as No not 1,000 dollars No no no no no no
работаете Нет не 1.000
listen let's agree right away And we wo
слушайте давай сразу так договоримся
n't do anything in dollars Yeah
А в долларах мы ничего не будем делать
good Well that's
хорошо
it there's nothing like
Да ну вот
that in 1 dollar and what in
всё нет ни такого в 1 долларов и что в
1000 dollars and what And when you had
1000 долларов а что А у вас когда было в
1000 dollars you bought cars for
1000 долларов вы машины покупали За
how much for example I ask well how much is
сколько например Я спрашиваю ну сколько
your dollar salary thousands of dollars
у вас долларов зарплата тысячи долларов
or
или
what No I don't have it in your dollars
как Нет у ня у меня не на ваших долларах
about you have 100,000 rubles
об у тебя 100000 руб
with
с
solid waste No  I don't have you 1000 dollars
ТБО Нет у меня нету у вас 1000 долларов
salary I don't earn in dollars I
зарплата я не в долларах зарабатываю Я в
earn in rubles in my own
рублях зарабатываю в своих
dear rubles on my own
родненький родненькие рубли на свои
teeth
зубы
what Why don't you spend your own
че Почему не тратишь свои родненькие
rubles on your own teeth
рубли на свои родненькие зубы
I don't want it it's none of your business everything no
Я не хочу это это не твоё дело всё не ну
why just doesn't everyone from Russia spend it it's
почему просто все из России не тратят
none of your business What difference does it make why what kind
это не твоё дело Какая те разница
of aggression I mean
почему что за агрессия Я имею в виду
why can't you make a normal dude with your salary
почему нельзя при вашей зарплате сделать
Yes I don't
нормальную челю Да я не
want look look
хочу вот ты смотри
how much do you spend on your
смотри ты сколько тратишь на свои
teeth your own there before you dollars you spend yato
зубы своих там до ты долларов тратишь
rubles dollars I have teeth and you don't
ято руб долларов У меня зубы есть а у
why is that No how much do you
тебя нет почему так Нет ты сколько
spend dollars look again I do
тратишь доллар ещё раз смотри я
n't give come on come on come on [ __ ]
не давай давай давай давай
you bastard dollars I spend
бля ско ты тти долларов я трачу В месяц
100 dollars a month on teeth salary is 9000
100 долларов на зубы зарплата 9000
dollars and you don't spend on you spend on teeth
долларов а ты не тратишь на ты на зубы
Zero is cool you don't have teeth
тратишь Ноль это кру у тебя нет зубов у
I have
меня есть
teeth The point is that  I have teeth and
зубы Суть в том что у меня есть зубы а у
you have no teeth and your wife is telling you now
тебя нет зубов и жена тебе сейчас
that's it, turn off and go to
говорит что всё давай отключайся да
sleep your wife is bossing you around and you have no teeth
спать иди жена тобой командует и зубов
Well,
нет Ну
what is it, I can chat with you, but
что такое я с тобой могу болтать е
look, she has
смотрите
4 hours, I'm not chatting with you,
у не 4 часа я с тобой не про болтаю ты
tell me why this is happening No, no Well, why not Why are you
скажи почему так получается Нет не Ну
offended or
почему нет Поче тако Ну уж обиделся что
something, explain to me, explain to
ли обясни мне объясни
me Why can't any Russians get
мне Почему никто из россиян не может
teeth, I'll explain, I'll explain,
зубы вставить объясню
explain,
Объясню да объяс
teeth, how are you doing it right So, yes So you're
зубы как ты правильно Так да Так ты мне
telling me Yes, first of all, look,
говоришь Да во-первых смотри
I don't
м я не
want to,
хочу
because I just don't want to, yes, well,
раз что что просто не хочешь да вот ну
tell me at least something like that Well,
вот что скажи мне хотя бы что-нибудь так
why don't you, what?
Ну а почему ты не че
I told you once, I told you
Я тебе сказал раз я тебе сказал
once, you just don't understand with
раз вот ты вот не понимаешь
your head, I don't
своей башкой не
understand, because I don't want to Why don't you want to,
понимаю раз я не хочу Почему не
I don't want to and that's it Well, in the whole world,
хочешь я не хочу и всё Ну во всм мире
people Just now, it's not clear why,
люди Просто теперь Тода непонятно почему
in the world, people want teeth, but only
вот во мире люди хотят зубы а только
Russians don't want teeth, everyone is toothless and that's it They don't want to
россияне не хотят зубы все без зубов и
I don't want to and that's it I
все Не хотят Я не хочу и
understood everything Or maybe you don't have money, you
понял А может у тебя нету денег
just don't have money, yes, yes  yes we have no money let's
просто денег нет да да да денег у нас
say so
тобой скажем так
why don't you
а почему ты не
want to
хо
say nothing Well
сказать нечего Ну
look tell
смотри
me Let's be honest You're just poor you have no
сказа Давай по чесноку Просто вы бедные
money you don't even have
нет у тебя денег у тебя даже
food in the fridge I guess you can't sweat it eh what Well bye
холодильнике еды походу не потов
And what do you think there should be some
э чем Ну пока А как по-вашему там
quail there or something I'm
перепёлкой бы что
even
ли Я даже
laughing Sorry I just can't
ржу Извини я уж просто не
quail I'm communicating
могу перепёлка я общаюсь
Poor thing Show me what you have in the
Бедняжка Покажи что у тебя есть в
fridge Show me with these these from behind
холодильнике Покажи этими этими сзади
your quail
своими перепёлка
there your product then I'll
там свою проду потом
think about it Everyone in Russia with bad
подумаю Все кто в России с плохими
teeth Everyone doesn't want In short, teeth
зубами Все не хотят Короче зубы вот не
they don't want they have money for it But they don't
хотят у них есть деньги на это Но не
want I don't know a single person
хотят Я не знаю ни одного человека у
who would have money for normal
которого были бы бабки на нормальные
teeth And he wouldn't want to look like a
зубы Да и он бы не хотел выглядеть как
normal person it's just that people who don't have
нормальный человек вот просто людей у
money for teeth I know people
которых нет деньги на зубы Я знаю людей
who don't have money They can be understood
которые у них нет денег Их можно понять
Yes he can't afford it Yes he won't be
Да он не может себе позволить Да его не
blamed for it Yes Well there are different people yes
обвинит за это да Ну люди разные есть да
someone is rich someone poor someone of
кто-то Богатый кто-то бедный кто-то
average income we are all different Yes you
среднего достатка мы все разные Да
can't judge a person for not
нельзя осуждать человека за то что он не
having access to  some material
имеет доступ к каким-то материальным
benefits Yes, that he lives poorer There are
благам Да что он живёт беднее Там че
others who can not understand him in this Yes,
другие можно не понимать его в этом Да
but let's
но
say to say that I do not want teeth and
а скажем говорить что я не хочу зубы и
say that I live great in this
говорит что я живу классно в этой
country I just do not want teeth this is
стране просто зубы не хочу это
nonsense you were sitting yesterday
бред вы вчера сидели
Today the
Сегодня
floor yesterday you were sitting here on the toilet and
пол вчера ты тут же на унитазе сидел и
today you are sitting
сегодня сидишь
in the
вле
VL [ __ ] You were sitting here yesterday and I turn on and
ВЛ сри Ты вчера тут сидел и я включаю и
you are sitting today you stupidly
ты сегодня сидишь ты тупо каждый день
sit on the toilet every day in chat
сидишь на унитазе в чат
roulette
рулетке
I agree froze let's
согласен застыл давай нормально
talk normally come on come on Easy easy
пообщаемся давай давай Легко легко
How much is your
Сколько у тебя
salary a lot Well how
зарплата много Ну сколько ну
much well how much Well let's at least make Well
сколько Ну давай хотя бы сделаем Ну
bets from something or somehow in rubles
ставки от чего-то или как-то в рублях
rubles rubles a hundred Cool Yes
рублях рублях стольник Прикольно Да
yesterday you also had a hundred and the
вчера у тебя тоже стольник был да не
salary has not changed salary and I
изменилась зарплата зарплата и я вчера
ask you yesterday And why if with your
тебя спрашиваю А почему если у тебя при
salary of a hundred you can't make yourself a chin
зарплате стольник ты не можешь себе челю
And what I can't make myself a face made a jaw
сделать А что я не могу себе рожу сделал
jaw teeth teeth teeth you have Well I do
челюсть челюсть зубы зубы зубы ты име Да
n't want to I said you
ну не хочу я же сказал ты тоже самое
said the same thing yesterday I understood everything stability
вчера говорил понял всё стабильность
stability Well, I got it, I got it, let's go
стабильность Ну ещё
No, let's go, let's go, let's go, now you
выхо Нет давай давай А давай теперь
can try it, try it, what's
обратку можно Попробуй попробуй Какая у
your
тебя
salary in Russian money, 9 million rubles a
зарплата на русские деньги 9 млн руб в
month, your
месяц
teeth look normal, but your
зубы выглядить нормально но нормальный
bag is normal, what do you eat, I eat everything, I eat everything, Well, okay, I'll ask it,
меш А что ешь всё ем всё ем Ну вот
but it's not very specific,
Ладно задам но очень не конкретный
of course, it's incorrect, that's what I said, the question is,
конечно некорректный я так сказал вопрос
how many children do you have in your family, four,
вот сколько у тебя в семье детей четверо
four
четверо
[music]
[музыка]
four, Well, that's two wives, I have two wives
четверо Ну это двух жн У меня две жены
at the same time, no, from one wife, two wives, I
одновременно
have two wives at the same time,
жены одновременно две жены А почему у
two wives, Why do you have two wives, Well, because I wanted to, I can afford it,
тебя две жены Ну потому что захотел могу
We are allowed by
позволить У нас Разрешено по
California law, California, And
законодательству Калифорнии Калифорнии А
in California, I mean, you can
в Калифорнии В смысле ты можешь с двумя
live
жёнами жить что да
with two wives, what, yes, you can, California law allows up to three, a little bit, I don't have time yet, where is that, where is that, let me have more detail now, please, tell me, Caliph of California, California, you can live there with two wives,
можешь там жить с двумя жёнами
and no, no, you can live with at least
а не не не так жить можешь хоть с
ten wives or husbands in general, And a
десятью жёнами или мужьями вообще А
married man can only be with two,
расписанный может быть только с двумя
yeah, yeah, that's how it is  yes, that is, you
Ага ага вот так вот вот да то есть жить
can live Look, I have two wives but I also
можно Смотри у меня те жены две но ещё
have two mistresses, they also live with us, I have
есть две любовницы они тоже живут с нами
a house Yes, each has their own part,
у меня домик Да у каждой есть свои часть
I already understood, I already understood Well, it's cool, it's cool
я уже понял понял уже
that I understood T Yes, I understood, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes,
понял Ну прикольно прикольно что понял Т
yes, I understand And what do I understand that
ну да ну понятно А что я я понимаю что у
your mouth is watering Because
тебя аж прям слюнка потекла Потому что
you haven't seen a woman there for 20 years
ты там женщину не видел лет 20 лет
20 well, no, that's kind of your
20 ну ну нет это как бы твоё
opinion, yours I'm a man, an alpha male,
мнение твоё Я мужчина Альфа самец у нас
in California, to raise the birth rate Yes, they
в Калифорнии для поднятия рождаемости Да
even allowed it under Biden Yes, what is possible
ещ при байдене разрешили Да что можно
if a man Yes, he can cope
если мужчина Да может справиться
morally and materially
морально и материально
with such a gang of girls Yes, you can, okay,
с такой бандой девчонок Да можно Лано
so that everything is for love, good luck, good luck
чтоб по любви всё было да удачи те удачи
You know what will happen a little further, don't [ __ ]
Ты знаешь что будет чуть-чуть дальше
No, I'm asking you, your
не Нет я тебя спрашиваю мне ваша
policy I'm just watching you from afar Well, I'm
политика Я просто смотрю вас издалека Ну
watching something and everything from afar, from afar, it's
и что-то смотрю и всё издалека
good that Trump banned all
издалека хорошо что Трамп запретил всех
these, in short, you yourself understood who Yes, so that the
этих короче ну ты сам понял кого Да
girls were normal
чтобы типа девчонки были Нормально
girls and not men That is, I will have
девчонками а не мужиками То есть у меня
more choice
больше будет выбор
nche and you know what Well, at least in 72 of these that
нче а ты знаешь что Ну ты хотя бы в 72
he accepted there at least
вот этих которые он там принял хотя бы
read something No, on the contrary, he canceled the Gene
что-нибудь читал Нет он наоборот отменил
Gene that he canceled how many genders the Gene canceled
Ген что он отменил ско Ген отменил лько
Yes
гендеров Да
this Well, read No, well, take Well,
это Ну почитай Нет ну брать Ну вот
honestly
честно
Read something It will be sad sad
Почитай что-то Будет грустно груст
poor people Listen, why are you putting your fingers in your mouth Well,
бедняки Слушай а что ты пальцы в ротик
I dont have teeth
Ну у меня же зубов
at least a finger yes yes
нет хотя бы пальце да да
subscribe to my Telegram right now
мня подпишись на мий Telegram прям зараз
he and
он а
while its very and very important YouTube is busy with
пок це дуже и дуже важливо YouTube заня
us through Geor in your ban and very many
нас через Геор в твый бан и дуже багато
videos I dont show people sometimes I dont show
вдео не показую людям вчасно не показуе
information about streams so that
информация про стримы тому для того щоб
we Mali operational links are written
ми Мали оперативный звязок пишиться
right now and while there in Telegram OKM videos there is
прямо зараз а пок там в телегра окм вдео
also interesting and useful information and we are
ще теж цикава и корисна информация и ми
sorry with you three times
повинни з вами трима постийний
operational linkage
оперативный звязок
independent in that chi will show you about This
незалежно в того чи покаже вам про Цей
YouTube Glory to Ukraine write
YouTube Слава Украине пиши